很高兴你回来欢迎你
It's good to have you back and to welcome you
迎接本节的第一个挑战。
to your very first challenge of this section.
在这一期中，我们将继续构建代码
And in this one, we will continue building on the code
我们已经在 HTML 基础部分中构建了它。
that we already built in the HTML fundamental section.
所以在我们的第一个大挑战之后，
So after our first big challenge,
我们最终得到了这段代码。
we ended up with this code.
所以这里有这个项目，请记住，
So with this project here, remember,
所以我现在想让你做的是建立在这个项目上
and so what I want you to do now is to build on this project
为了实现这一点，基本上。
in order to achieve this, basically.
所以在这里你看到我们有一些大写的文本，
So here you see that we have some text in upper case,
这个，这个，
this one, this one,
这个标题之间有一些灰色的背景颜色。
there is some gray background color between this heading.
您还看到这里有一些特殊的样式。
You also see that there are some special styles here.
这个文本要大得多。
This text is way larger.
按钮的样式是这样的。
The button is styled like this.
因此，当我们将其悬停时，链接的样式也会有所不同。
So when we hover it and also the link is styled differently.
整个组件周围有一个大的黑色边框。
There is a big black border around the entire component.
所以整个文章元素，我想就是这样。
So this entire article element, and I think that's it.
此外，这里的这些列表图标现在是方形的。
Also, these list icons here are now square.
为了实现这一点，您可以进行实验
And to achieve this, you can experiment
具有不同的列表样式属性值，
with different values of the list style property,
但这也不是很重要。
but this one is also not really important.
所以真正重要的是这种悬停风格。
So what's really important is this hover style.
所以基本上链接本身是黑色的。
So basically the link on itself is black.
然后一旦我们悬停它，
And then once we hover it,
所发生的只是下划线消失了。
all that happens is that the underline disappears.
然后在这里，记住这实际上是
Then down here, remember that this is actually
按钮元素和按钮也可以具有悬停状态。
a button element and buttons can also have hover states.
现在，与链接不同，它们没有链接
Now, unlike links, they do not have the link
或访问过的伪类，
or visited pseudo-class,
但是您仍然可以为悬停伪类指定样式。
but you can still specify styles for the hover pseudo-class.
所以我想让你做的是
And so what I want you to do is that
当我们悬停这个按钮时，基本上是为了反转颜色。
when we hover this button is basically to invert the colors.
所以背景是黑色的，现在是白色的
So the background was black and now it's white
之前的文字是白色的，现在是黑色的。
and the text was white before, and now it is black.
这么好的效果，
So a nice effect like this,
并且不用担心正确的颜色
and don't really worry about the correct colors
以及这里的正确字体大小。
and about the correct font sizes here.
所以现在只需使用任何值，
So just use any values for now,
因为我的目标是你真的练习
because my goal with this is that you really practice
属性本身和值
the properties themselves and the values
并不是真正重要的。
are not really what matters.
好的？
Okay?
所以作为这个挑战的起点，
So as a starting point for this challenge,
请使用您最终得到的代码
please use the code that you ended up with
在你最后一次编码挑战之后。
after your last coding challenge.
所以在 HTML 基础部分结束后，
So after the end of the HTML fundamental section,
如果由于某种原因您不再拥有该代码，
and if for some reason you don't have that code anymore,
或者如果你没有做那个挑战，
or if you didn't do that challenge,
然后我还将在此视频中包含一个链接
then I will also include a link in this video
在哪里可以找到启动代码，
where you can find the starter code,
这样您就可以从那里开始工作。
so that you can start working from there.
所以这是一个很大的挑战。
So this is kind of a big challenge.
所以它应该至少需要你半个小时，
So it should take you at least probably half an hour,
也许更多一点来完成这个。
maybe a bit more to finish this.
而且根本不是问题
And it's not a problem at all,
如果你必须回到我们一起编写的代码
If you have to go back to the code that we wrote together
在讲座期间。
during the lectures.
所以你不必记住
So you don't have to have memorized
此时所有的属性名称。
all of the property names at this point.
如果您需要查看其中的一些，这是完全正常的。
It's completely normal if you need to look some of them up.
好的。
Okay.
所以不要因为这样做而感到难过。
So don't feel bad for doing that.
我想让你自己写一些 CSS，
What I want you to do is to write some CSS on your own,
我相信你会这样做的。
and I'm sure that you will do that.
所以，等你准备好后，再见。
So see you back here, once you are ready.
欢迎回来！
Welcome back!
我希望你在解决这个挑战时玩得很开心
And I hope that you had a great time solving this challenge
而且你玩得很开心，我们不要浪费任何时间
and that you had a lot of fun and let's not waste any time
并立即开始工作。
and get to work right away.
我将从身体开始
And I will start with the body
我会给它一个无衬线字体系列。
and I will give it a sans-serif font family.
所以，无衬线字体。
So, sans-serif.
因此，正如我们在上一节课中了解到的，
And so, as we learned in the last lecture,
此字体系列设置为 sans-serif 现在将被继承
this font family is set to sans-serif will now be inherited
对所有其他元素，好吗？
to all of the other elements, alright?
所以这本身就是一个很大的变化。
And so that already in itself is a big change.
现在，我想在这里做的另一件事，
Now, another thing that I want to do here,
这个对你来说不是强制性的
and this one was not mandatory for you
因为其实我都没提过
because I actually didn't even mention it,
但我想在这里增加行高。
but I want to increase the line height here.
这是另一个属性
And this is another one of those property
这实际上确实得到了继承。
that actually does get inherited.
并在此处添加一些行高
And by adding some line height here
在所有元素之间，
between all the elements,
我们之间有更多的喘息空间，
we get a little bit more breathing space here between,
尤其是这些 LI 元素。
especially these LI elements.
好的，现在让我们从顶部开始工作
Okay, and now let's simply start working from the top
到此 HTML 代码的底部。
to the bottom of this HTML code here.
所以从文章开始，
So starting with the article,
我们将首先在它周围添加黑色边框。
we'll start by adding that black border around it.
所以在这里，让我们给它一类产品
So here, let's give it a class of product
我现在将开始在每个元素上使用类。
and I will now start using classes on every single element.
但是再一次，你不必完全那样做。
But once again, you wouldn't have to do it exactly that way.
所以如果你的结果和我的一样，
So if your result looks the same as mine,
那么就没有必要改变任何东西了。
then there is no need to change anything.
好的。
All right.
所以我在这里使用了一个四像素。
So I used a four pixel here.
也许使用其他东西，但这并不重要。
Maybe use something else, but that's not really important.
很好太棒了。
Okay, nice.
现在，我们有这个h2，
Now, here we have this h2,
所以我称之为“产品名称”。
so I'm calling that the "product title".
所以产品标题，让我们看看这里。
So product title, and let's take a look here.
所以文字在中间。
So the text is in the center.
有这个背景颜色，它是大写的。
There is this background color and it is uppercase.
所以让我们这样做。
So let's do that.
文本居中对齐，
Text align of center,
字体大小，比如说，22 像素，
a font size, let's say, of 22 pixels,
那么它也是大写的，对吧？
then it was also uppercase, right?
所以这是文本转换大写，
So that's text transform uppercase,
最后是我们所拥有的微妙的背景颜色。
and finally that subtle background color that we had.
我将再次使用讲座中的那个，F7F7F7。
00:06:29,130​​ --> 00:06:32,670
确实，这看起来相当不错。
And I will use again the one from the lectures, F7F7F7.
And indeed, that looks quite nice.
所以让我们继续下一个。
And so let's move on to the next one.
让我们在这里添加一些评论
Let's just add some comments here
使其更容易理解。
to make it easier to understand.
在 CodePen 中，实际上完全相同的快捷方式有效
And here in CodePen, actually the exact same shortcut works
就像在 VSCode 中一样，所以这是命令或控制斜线，好吧。
as in VSCode, so that's command or control slash, all right.
所以接下来，让我们把文字放大一点
So next up, let's make the text a little bit bigger
让我们也在这里更改这个免费送货标签。
and let's also change this free shipping label here.
所以你会看到，是的，价格更高。
So you'll see that, yeah, the price is bigger.
然后这里的免费送货有点像，只是一个标签，
And then this free shipping here is kind of a, just a label,
对？
Right?
这实际上会更有意义
And this will actually make a bit more sense
一旦我们把它变成一个漂亮的布局，
once we transform this into a nice layout,
但重要的是文字很小
but what matters is that the text is quite small
和大写和浅灰色。
and uppercase and a lighter gray.
所以让我们现在做所有这些。
So let's do all of that now.
所以这个叫“价格”，这个叫“运费”。
So this one is called "price" and this one, "shipping".
所以请注意我在这一点上做得非常快，
So notice how I'm doing this quite fast here at this point,
因为我们已经了解了所有这些属性
because we already learned about all of these properties
我真的只是想解决这里的挑战
and I'm really just trying to solve the challenge here
和你一起，你希望已经做到了
together with you which you hopefully already did
以前靠自己。
on your own before.
所以这是更多，
So this is more,
我喜欢回顾大部分的东西
I like to review most of the stuff
我们以前已经做过。
that we already did before.
所以我在这里调用我们代码的这种部分，
So I'm calling this kind of section of our code here,
产品信息，然后是价格。
product information and then price.
在这里，假设我们想要 24 像素的字体大小。
And here let's say we want a font size of 24 pixels.
好的。
Nice.
现在，至于运输，
And now, as for the shipping,
所以发货，还要注意我是如何只使用类的
so shipping and also notice how I'm only ever using classes
从来没有ID。
and never IDs.
再说一次，这基本上是为了证明我们的代码，
And so again, that's to basically future proof our code,
就像我在之前的一堂课中解释的那样
such as I explained in one of the earlier lectures
在部分，对吧？
in the section, right?
所以这里的字体大小有点偏小。
So the font size here is a bit on the small side.
所以12像素。
So 12 pixels.
记住是大写。
Remember that's uppercase.
现在我们还有什么？
And now what else do we have?
字体粗细也是粗体。
The font weight was also bold.
让我们看看还有什么？
And let's see what else?
哦，是的，我们有这样的浅色。
Oh yeah, we have this like lighter color.
所以，让我们在这里使用 777。
So, let's use a 777 here.
而这个颜色，你本来可以想出的
And this color, you could have like come up with
在 VSCode 颜色选择器中，对吗？
in the VSCode color picker, right?
对我来说，这个值就像一个默认值
For me, this value is just already like a default
当我需要较浅的灰色时，在我的脑海中。
in my head when I need a lighter gray color.
当然，对你来说，这也将伴随着练习而来。
And for you, of course, this will also come with practice.
好的。
All right.
现在，无论如何，让我们转到此处的链接。
Now, anyway, let's move on to the link here.
所以这就是这里。
So that's this one here.
将此称为“更多信息”，
Calling this one, "more info",
所以，更多信息。
so, more info.
现在记住这是一个链接
And now remember that this is a link
它确实有一个 href 属性。
and it does have a href property.
因此，我们现在应该在这里使用
And so therefore, here we should now use
链接伪类，好吗？
the link pseudo-class, okay?
所以这是最好的做法。
So that's the best practice.
始终为不同的链接状态设置实际样式。
Always to actually style the different link states.
所以唯一真正改变的是颜色，
So the only thing that actually changes is the color,
如果我没记错的话应该变成黑色。
which should become black if I remember it correctly.
对？
Right?
和悬停状态相同，唯一不同的是
And the hover state is the same with the only difference
下划线消失了，活动的也一样。
that the underline is gone and the same for the active.
所以我只是点击它，它看起来仍然一样。
So I just clicked and it still looks the same.
所以让我们把它翻译成代码。
So let's translate that into code.
所以，悬停，现在我说的是文字装饰
So, hover, and now what I said is that text decoration
是没有，我也说同样是真的
is none and I also said that the same is true
对于活跃的，所以而不是仅仅复制这条规则，
for the active and so instead of just copying this rule,
我可以只复制选择器并将其作为列表执行。
I can just copy the selector and do this as a list.
所以我希望这发生在悬停和活动时。
So I want this to happen on hover and on active.
希望你注意到我们实际上失踪了
And hopefully you noticed that we are actually missing
州之一。
one of the states.
所以让我们在这里简单地添加它。
And so let's simply add that here.
这就是访问状态。
So that's the visited state.
所以我之前提到过，我们应该始终指定
So I mentioned before that we should always specify
所有四个状态，并且始终按此顺序。
all the four states and always in this order.
因此，首先链接，然后访问，然后悬停，然后激活。
So, first link, then visited, then hover and then active.
在这种情况下，链接和访问状态发生了
And in this case, the link and the visited state happened
相同，悬停和活动也是如此。
to be the same and the same goes for hover and active.
所以这和预期的一样工作得很好。
And so that works nicely just as expected.
好的。
Okay.
所以这部分的代码基本上就是
So this section here of the code is basically
产品信息。
the product information.
现在在这里，我们有一些产品细节。
And now down here, we have kind of the product details.
所以这里的所有这些，我们可以称之为产品细节。
So all of this here, we can call it product details.
所以让我们像ano一样添加在我们的代码中这里有分隔符。
So let's add like another separator here inside of our code.
所以这很好地在视觉上划分我们的代码
And so this is nice to visually divide our code
分成不同的部分。
into different sections.
在这里，我们有详细的标题，
Here, we have the details title,
然后让我们调用列表，详细信息列表。
and then let's call the list, the details list.
好吧，让我们从这里抓住这个。
Okay, let's grab this from here.
所以我们不必重新写一遍。
So we don't have to write it all over again.
然后这里是列表，实际上让我们从它开始。
And then here the list, and actually let's start with that.
所以我告诉你做一点实验
So I told you to experiment a little bit
使用列表样式属性，
with the list style property,
这在 CodePen 中实际上并不适用。
which doesn't really work here in CodePen.
我的意思是实验，因为值没有显示出来，
I mean the experimenting, because the values do not show up,
就像他们在 VSCode 中所做的那样，
like they do in VSCode,
但也许你是在 VSCode 中做到的
but maybe you did it in VSCode
在那里你可以看到其中一个选项
and there you could see that one of the options
是将其设置为正方形。
is to set it to square.
所以它看起来像这样，所以它非常适合
And so then it looks like this, so it fits nicely
其余的，我们这里的四四方方的布局。
the rest of, our kind of boxy layout here.
好的。
Okay.
然后在这里，产品细节，
And then here, the product details,
让我们像其他标题一样将其设为大写。
let's just make it uppercase like the other heading.
所以，文本转换大写
So, text transform upper case
字体大小为 16 像素。
and a font size of 16 pixels.
不错，漂亮
Okay, beautiful.
看起来已经差不多了
That looks already almost the same
除了这里的按钮。
except here for the button.
所以这也应该很容易。
And so that should be easy as well.
所以让我们在这里创建一个新部分
So let's create a new section here
仅用于按钮和这段非常小的代码。
just for the button and in this very small piece of code.
现在，当然没有必要这样做。
Now, of course it wouldn't be necessary to do it like this.
因此，要在此处添加所有这些评论，
So to add all of these comments here,
但我只是想让你开始养成习惯
but I just want you to start to get into the habits
组织你自己的代码一点点。
of organizing your own code a little bit.
好的？
Okay?
所以这里的这个按钮，我称之为“添加购物车”。
So this button here, I'm calling it "add cart".
现在让我们从背景颜色开始，设置为黑色。
And now let's start with the background color, set to black.
让我们来看看。
Let's see.
但是现在我们得到了你在这里看到的这个非常丑陋的边界。
But now we get this very ugly border that you see here.
所以我不知道我们以前是否真的这样做过。
So I don't know if we actually did this before.
可能，我们没有。
Probably, we didn't.
所以这当然不是什么大问题，
So it's not a big deal, of course,
如果你没有在这里做这部分，
if you didn't do this part here,
所以将边框设置为无。
so setting the border to none.
但无论如何，我们应该将颜色设置为白色。
But anyway, the color we should set to white.
所以我们可以使用 CSS 颜色名称来做到这一点，
And so we can do that using the CSS color name,
或者我们当然可以做十六进制代码。
or we could of course do the hex code.
所以 FFF 的十六进制表示法
So the hexadecimal notation of FFF
这是完全相同的事情。
which is exactly the same thing.
然后让我们让它更大一点。
Then let's make it a bit bigger.
字体大小，20 像素
Font size, 20 pixels
再次，文本转换为 20，
and again, a text transform of 20,
好吧，当然不是 20 像素，而是大写。
well, not of 20 pixels, of course, but of uppercase.
很好，所以我认为这看起来一样。
Nice, so I think that looks the same.
而现在我们基本上只需要相反的东西。
And now we just need the opposite basically.
哦，我们还需要在这里添加这样的光标。
Oh, and we also need to add like this cursor here.
所以这个指针，so the，就像手一样。
So this pointer, so the, like the hand.
因为通常在按钮上，默认情况下不会出现。
because usually on a button, that doesn't appear by default.
所以这肯定是我之前没有向你展示过的房产，
So this is certainly a property I didn't show you before,
但现在让我给你看。
but let me show it to you now.
所以我们可以将光标设置为指针。
So we can set the cursor to pointer.
所以现在它看起来像一个链接。
And so now it looks like a link.
所以你看到了。
So you see it.
现在我们有手，就像我们在这里一样。
Now we have the hand here just like we had here.
伟大的！而现在，正如我之前告诉你的，
Great! And now, as I told you before,
您现在可以设置悬停伪类。
you can now set the hover pseudo-class.
好吧，因为这是一个按钮
All right, because this is a button
我们当然可以悬停它。
and we can of course hover it.
所以我们可以指定悬停伪类。
And so we can specify the hover pseudo-class.
实际上，我们可以在所有元素上做到这一点
And actually, we can do that on all elements
但通常，它没有多大意义。
but usually, it doesn't make a lot of sense.
所以无论如何，我们在这里要做的基本上就是
So anyway, all we want to do here is basically
反转颜色。
to invert the colors.
所以现在颜色应该是黑色并保持一致，
So now the color should be black and to keep it consistent,
让我们使用十六进制表示法，这里也一样。
let's use the hexadecimal notation, and the same here.
所以我喜欢以这种方式保持一致。
So I like to keep things consistent in this way.
然后背景颜色现在应该是白色的。
And then the background color should now be white.
好的，确实，这行得通。
Okay, and indeed, that works.
所以我认为有了这个，
So I think that with this,
我们这里的项目现在看起来完全一样
our project here now looks exactly the same
作为演示代码。
as the demo code.
伟大的！
Great!
所以我希望这不是太难而且你玩得开心
So I hope that wasn't too hard and that you had some fun
并且您至少能够做到其中一些。
and that you were able to do at least some of it.
因此，如果您需要喜欢，请将您的代码与我的代码进行比较，
So, in case you need to like, compare your code with mine,
我将包含指向此挑战的最终代码的链接
I will include a link to the final code of this challenge
在这个讲座的某个地方。
somewhere into this lecture.
话虽如此，我们下节课见，
And with that being said, I'll see you in the next lecture,
这是本节最重要的部分之一。
which is one of the most important ones of this section.